Mustafa Dalğa Front End Developer

https://github.com/mustafadalga

https://medium.com/@mustafadalga

https://www.npmjs.com/~mustafadalga

in https://linkedin.com/in/mustafadalga/

https://stackoverflow.com/users/10636297/mustafa

• https://codepen.io/mustafadalga

https://gist.github.com/mustafadalga

Profile

I see software development as a hobby rather than a job.

I have had the opportunity to use many technologies by developing desktop and web applications for 6 years. I continue to learn and grow in life using research skills and accumulated experience, following a "be your own teacher" philosophy.

Javascript is my main programming language. I share the projects I have developed to learn and improve myself on Github as open source. I am working as a Front-end developer at Heybooster.

My vision is to develop myself as a high quality software developer/engineer following the ethical code of hackers.

Professional Experience

Heybooster, Front End Developer 🛮

09/2020 - present

Technologies: Javascript, Typescript, Vue JS, Vuex, Webpack, Vite.js, Vitest, testing-library, vue-test-utils, HTML5, SCSS(CSS3), Tailwind CSS

I had the following tasks in the app.heybooster.ai .

Responsibilities

- J Maintainable and sustainability of front end projects
- J Creating a sustainable architecture
- J Responsive Design

Responsive development of non-Responsive designs by rearranging or rewriting them

- J Improving Web performance
- Improvements to improve site transitions and user experience in addition to increasing site speed
- Detecting and resolving bugs for front-end development
- → Productivity Improvement
- √ Improving legacy code
- ✓ Correcting or rewriting codes according to clean code principles.
- J Defining code writing principles to be used within the team to write code better and improve code readability and sharing them with the team
- J Creating and using Vuex modules by actively using Vuex to keep data more organized and easier to manage
- J Testing all improvements/fixed bugs
- J Upgrade Vue v2 to Vue v3: https://medium.com/heybooster/adventures-of-a-front-end-developer-migration-of-front-end-project-e3b949bdde90

Free Software and Open Source Developer, Software Developer 2

Technologies: Javascript, Vue.js, Jquery, Python , PHP , HTML5 , CSS3 ,Bootstrap

Development of projects using various technologies

- Real Time Two Player Intelligence Game Tactix | React.js
- Tooltip generator | React JS ☑
- Connect Four Realtime Intelligence Game | Vue.js 🗷
- Quiz Application Vue.js ☑
- Forex Exchange ☑
- Music Player | Vue.js ☑
- Computer Lab Automation | Vue.js ☑

02/2019 - 10/2020

- Typing Game | Vue.js ☑
- Multi Level Memory Game | Vue.js ☑
- Multi Level Puzzle Game | Vue.js ☑
- Breakout Game | Vue.js 🗷
- Zou Farm Landing Page ☑
- Heybooster Landing Page ☑
- Foundation Landing Page ☑
- Tour and Travel WebSite Landing Page ☑

Private Procare Health Services, Front End Developer

08/2017 - 02/2019

Technologies:Pure Javascript, Jquery, HTML, CSS, PHP

Responsibilities

- J Responsive Design
- J Development of <u>privateprocare.com</u> ☑
- J Development of a platform for human resource management enprestis.com ☑

Vizyon Dijital, Software Developer

04/2017 - 08/2017

Technologies:PHP, Pure Javascript, Jquery, HTML, CSS

Responsibilities

- J Responsive Design
- J Detecting and resolving bugs for front-end development
- J Improving legacy code

Skills

Vue.js | React.js | Javascript | Typescript | SCSS | CSS3 | Vuex | Webpack | Vite.js | Redux toolkit HTML5 | Jquery | Bootstrap , Materialize CSS, Tailwind CSS | Git | Vitest

Projects

Tactix | Real Time Two Player Intelligence Game 2

07/2022 - 08/2022

React.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Node.js, Socket.io, Redux Toolkit, TailwindCSS, Vite.js

Tooltip Generator, React JS, Redux Toolkit, Tailwind CSS, HTML5, CSS

Connection Four Realtime Intelligence Game,

Vue.js, Firebase, Materialize CSS, HTML5, CSS3 ☑

Quiz Application, Vue.js, Typescript, Vite.js, SCSS, CSS3

Forex Exchange, Vue.js , Javascript, SCSS, Socket.io

Computer Lab Automation, Vue.js, Laravel, PostgreSQL, CSS, HTML, Bootstrap ☑

Music Player, Vue.js, Vuex, SCSS - CSS3, HTML5 2

Typing Game, Vue.js, CSS3, HTML5

Multi Level Memory Game, Vue.js, SCSS - CSS3, HTML5 2

Multi Level Puzzle Game, Vue.js, SCSS - CSS3, HTML5 2

Breakout Game, Vue.js, Canvas, CSS3, HTML5 ☑

Zou - Farm Landing Page, JavaScript, SCSS - CSS3 , HTML5 🛮

Heybooster Landing Page, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript ☑

Foundation Web Site UI Design, JavaScript, SCSS - CSS3, HTML5

Tour and Travel Landing Page Web Design, JavaScript, SCSS-CSS3, HTML5 2

Education

Marmara University, GPA:3.22 / 4 | | 84.7 / 100 CEIT(Computer Education and Instructional Technology)

2016 – 2020 İstanbul, Turkey

Cizre Technical High School, *GPA* = 3.76 /Top scoring student Information Technologies - Top scoring student

2011 - 2015 Turkey

Certificates

• Cambly Certificate of Accomplishment 🛮

• Certificate of Completion | English Language ☑

Publications

Techinal Blog Posts, https://medium.com/@mustafadalga ☑

References

Recommendations, https://www.linkedin.com/in/mustafadalga/details/recommendations/